# Source: grammatikk.com © Kjell H. Ullestad
- question: "I see two boys."
  answer: "Jeg ser to gutter."

- question: "I see the black cat."
  answer: "Jeg ser den svarte katten."

- question: "I see that man."
  answer: "Jeg ser den mannen."

- question: "I see the brother."
  answer: "Jeg ser broren."

- question: "I see the big house."
  answer: "Jeg ser det store huset."

- question: "I see four bikes."
  answer: "Jeg ser fire sykler."

- question: "I see this book."
  answer: "Jeg ser denne boka/boken."

- question: "I see the girls."
  answer: "Jeg ser jentene."

- question: "I see three new jackets."
  answer: "Jeg ser tre nye jakker."

- question: "I see these cars."
  answer: "Jeg ser disse bilene."

- question: "I see many chairs."
  answer: "Jeg ser mange stoler."

- question: "I see the man."
  answer: "Jeg ser mannen."

- question: "I see a brown house."
  answer: "Jeg ser et brunt hus."

- question: "I see a girl."
  answer: "Jeg ser ei/en jente."

- question: "I see the big child."
  answer: "Jeg ser det store barnet."

- question: "I see many students."
  answer: "Jeg ser mange studenter."

- question: "I see an old house."
  answer: "Jeg ser et gammelt hus."

- question: "I see many old men."
  answer: "Jeg ser mange gamle menn."

- question: "I see the young boys."
  answer: "Jeg ser de unge guttene."

- question: "I see those houses."
  answer: "Jeg ser de husene."

- question: "I see the happy child."
  answer: "Jeg ser det glade barnet."

- question: "I see the books."
  answer: "Jeg ser bøkene."

- question: "I see a father."
  answer: "Jeg ser en far."

- question: "I see the pretty houses."
  answer: "Jeg ser de pene/fine husene."

- question: "I see that mother."
  answer: "Jeg ser den mora."

- question: "I see a tired boy."
  answer: "Jeg ser en trøtt gutt."

- question: "I see this child."
  answer: "Jeg ser dette barnet."

- question: "I see the pen."
  answer: "Jeg ser pennen."

- question: "I see a beautiful child."
  answer: "Jeg ser et vakkert barn."

- question: "I see those newspapers."
  answer: "Jeg ser de avisene."

- question: "I see the new house."
  answer: "Jeg ser det nye huset."

- question: "I see many yellow pens."
  answer: "Jeg ser mange gule penner."

- question: "I see the father."
  answer: "Jeg ser faren."

- question: "I see the red car."
  answer: "Jeg ser den røde bilen."

- question: "I see these men."
  answer: "Jeg ser disse mennene."

- question: "I see this pretty book."
  answer: "Jeg ser denne pene/fine boka/boken."

- question: "I see two friends."
  answer: "Jeg ser to venner."

- question: "I see an old friend."
  answer: "Jeg ser en gammel venn."

- question: "I see this old friend."
  answer: "Jeg ser denne gamle vennen."

- question: "I see the cats."
  answer: "Jeg ser kattene."

- question: "I see the shop."
  answer: "Jeg ser butikken."

- question: "I see the yellow bananas."
  answer: "Jeg ser de gule bananene."

- question: "I see those cars."
  answer: "Jeg ser de bilene."

- question: "I see the cup."
  answer: "Jeg ser koppen."

- question: "I see many white cups."
  answer: "Jeg ser mange hvite kopper."

- question: "I see a green book."
  answer: "Jeg ser ei/en grønn bok."

- question: "I see this man."
  answer: "Jeg ser denne mannen."

- question: "I see this white house."
  answer: "Jeg ser dette hvite huset."

- question: "I see that boy."
  answer: "Jeg ser den gutten."

- question: "I see the happy friend."
  answer: "Jeg ser den glade vennen."

